setalarmclock.net 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy | SetAlarmClock.net 👍

_By continuing to use SetAlarmClock.net’s websites, you consent to the use of cookies._

## 1\. INTRODUCTION

This privacy notice provides you with details of how we collect and process your personal data through your use of our site **SetAlarmClock.net**.

By providing us with your data, you warrant to us that you are over 13 years of age.

**Ing. Michal Masliš** is the data controller and is responsible for your personal data (referred to as "we", "us" or "our" in this privacy notice).

**Contact Details**

Our full details are:

Full name of responsible person: **Ing. Michal Masliš** (company owner)

Full name of legal entity: **Amasweb s.r.o.**

EU VAT number: **SK2023850246**

Email address: **info [at] setalarmclock.net**

Postal address: **Volgogradská 76, 080 01, Prešov, Slovakia**

If you are not happy with any aspect of how we collect and use your data, you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues ([ _www.ico.org.uk_](https://www.ico.org.uk/)). We should be grateful if you would contact us first if you do have a complaint so that we can try to resolve it for you.

It is very important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. Please let us know if at any time your personal information changes by emailing us at **info [at] setalarmclock.net**

## 2\. WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

Personal data means any information capable of identifying an individual. It does not include anonymised data.

We may process certain types of personal data about you as follows:

  * **Technical Data** may include your internet protocol addresses, browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions, time zone setting and location, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this site. 
  * **Usage Data** may include information about how you use our website, products and services.

We may also process Aggregated Data from your personal data but this data does not reveal your identity and as such in itself is not personal data. An example of this is where we review your Usage Data to work out the percentage of website users using a specific feature of our site. If we link the Aggregated Data with your personal data so that you can be identified from it, then it is treated as personal data.

**Sensitive Data**

We do not collect any Sensitive Data about you. Sensitive data refers to data that includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data. We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

## 3\. HOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

We collect data about you through a variety of different methods including:

  * **Direct interactions:** You may provide data by filling in forms on our site (or otherwise) or by communicating with us by post, phone, email or otherwise, including when you: 
    * Give us feedback or send us suggestions or bug reports
  * **Automated technologies or interactions:** As you use our site, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and usage patterns. We collect this data by using cookies, server logs and similar technologies. Log files on our web server are automatically deleted after several days' time. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites that use our cookies. Please see our cookie policy below for further details.
  * **Third parties or publicly available sources:** We may receive personal data about you from various third parties and public sources as set out below: 
    * Cloudflare, Inc. (our Web Security and Peformance provider)
    * Google / Google Plus / YouTube / Google's DART & AdSense
    * Analytics providers such as Google based outside the EU
    * Advertising networks such as Google AdSense and its partner networks based inside and outside the EU

##  4.HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We will only use your personal data when legally permitted. The most common uses of your personal data are:

  * Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests
  * Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation
  * To protect our website and web server against cyber-attacks
  * To serve personalized advertising, which is the sole source of funding for our website and its various web services

Generally, we do not rely on consent as a legal ground for processing the personal data described above.

**Purposes for processing your personal data**

Set out below is a description of the ways we intend to use your personal data and the legal grounds on which we will process such data. We have also explained what our legitimate interests are where relevant.

We may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground, depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please email us at **info [at] setalarmclock.net** if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.

**Purpose/Activity**

| 

**Type of data**

| 

**Lawful basis for processing**  
  
---|---|---  
  
To administer and protect our business and our site (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data)

| 

 (a) Technical

| 

(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise

(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation  
  
To deliver relevant content and advertisements to you and measure and understand the effectiveness of our advertising

| 

 (a) Usage

 (b) Technical

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy  
  
To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences

| 

(a) Technical

(b) Usage

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our site updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy  
  
**Change of purpose**

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to find out more about how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please email us at **info [at] setalarmclock.net**.

If we need to use your personal data for a purpose unrelated to the purpose for which we collected the data, we will notify you and we will explain the legal ground of processing.

We may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent where this is required or permitted by law.

## 5\. DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below for the purposes set out in the table in paragraph 4 above:

  * Service providers who provide IT and system administration services
  * Security services who protect our website against malicious activity
  * Third parties to whom we sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets.

We require all third parties to whom we transfer your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We only allow such third parties to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

## 6\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

Countries outside of the European Economic Area ( **EEA** ) do not always offer the same levels of protection to your personal data, so European law has prohibited transfers of personal data outside of the EEA unless the transfer meets certain criteria.

Many of our third parties service providers are based outside the European Economic Area ( **EEA** ) so their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA.

Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we do our best to ensure a similar degree of security of data by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:

  * We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission; or
  * Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts or codes of conduct or certification mechanisms approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe; or
  * Where we use providers based in the United States, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the **EU-US Privacy Shield** which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US.

If none of the above safeguards is available, we may request your explicit consent to the specific transfer. You will have the right to withdraw this consent at any time.

Please email us at **info [at] setalarmclock.net** if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA.

## 7\. DATA SECURITY

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know such data. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

## 8\. DATA RETENTION

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see below for further information.

In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

## 9\. YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data. These include the right to:

  * Request access to your personal data.
  * Request correction of your personal data.
  * Request erasure of your personal data.
  * Object to processing of your personal data.
  * Request restriction of processing your personal data.
  * Request transfer of your personal data.
  * Right to withdraw consent.

You can see more about these rights at:

https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please email us at **info [at] setalarmclock.net**.

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.

## 10\. THIRD-PARTY LINKS

This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.

## 11\. COOKIES

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. For more information about the cookies we use, please see our cookie policy below.

### What is a cookie?

Cookies are small pieces of information, stored in simple text files, placed on your computer by a website. Cookies can be read by the website on your subsequent visits. The information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing habits on the web page, or a unique identification number so that the website can "remember" you on your return visit. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have furnished such information to the website.

If you do not want to allow cookies [or only allow the use of certain types of cookies], please refer to your browser settings, which should allow you to accept or deny cookies (for more information on this, see ‘How to manage and disable cookies’ below). You can also use the browser settings to withdraw your consent to the use of cookies at any time.

By disabling certain categories of cookies, you may be prevented from accessing some of the features on our website.

### How does SetAlarmClock.net use cookies?

SetAlarmClock.net uses the following cookie types:

Cookie type | Cookie purpose  
---|---  
Functionality | These cookies allows to remember choices you make and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to some settings.  
To make the site faster and to increase your privacy, in many cases we use instead of cookies another method - local storage, so the information about your settings (e.g. alarm/timer time, message, sound, counter progress...) could remain only in your computer and they are not send to the server.  
Performance | These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. SetAlarmClock.net uses first-party analytics cookies for this purpose.  
Targeting Cookies | Targeting cookies remember individual websites you have visited and help SetAlarmClock.net to present relevant and targeted online advertising to you. Targeting cookies may be placed on your machine when you visit a SetAlarmClock.net website page. When targeting cookies have been placed on your device, they can be recognised by subsequent websites you visit, and this allows those sites to present targeted SetAlarmClock.net and third party advertising to you. While targeting cookies can track your visits around different websites and identify if you are a user of SetAlarmClock.net, the information collected is anonymous.  
Users can set their browsers to accept or reject all, or certain, cookies. If you would like more information about how to manage cookies, please see the section below headed, ‘How to manage and disable cookies’.  
Expiration (How long cookies last)*  
---  
Session Cookies | These cookies are added when a visitor starts to browse our website or interacts with a specific feature and are deleted when the browser is closed.  
Persistent Cookies | These cookies are added when a visitor starts to browse our website or interacts with a specific feature, but may remain stored on your device until a certain termination date is reached (in terms of minutes, days or years from the creation/update of the cookie).  
  
*To be confirmed. 

Please take note of the following information with regard to the Google third party cookies used on our website:

### Google Universal Analytics

#### What is Google Analytics?

Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies in order to evaluate your use of SetAlarmClock.net’s website. Browsers do not share cookies across domains.

#### How Google Analytics Works

Google does not collect or store personal information. Google Analytics prohibits the tracking or collection of personal information or association of personal information with web analytics information. Google Analytics does not report the actual IP address information to Google Analytics customers.

#### What Google Analytics features are enabled by SetAlarmClock.net?

The following Google Analytics Advertising features are enabled in respect of SetAlarmClock.net’s use of Google Analytics:

_User ID_ -This allows SetAlarmClock.net to associate multiple sessions (and any activity within those sessions) with a unique ID, in this case an ID derived from online interactions with SetAlarmClock.net. When the unique ID and any related engagement data is sent to Google Analytics, all activity is attributed to one anonymous user who is not personally identifiable in the reports.

With the unique ID, SetAlarmClock.net can get a more accurate user count, analyse the signed-in user experience, and get access to the new cross-device reports.

In addition with a unique ID, SetAlarmClock.net can present more relevant SetAlarmClock.net and third party advertising to a user as the unique ID can indicate if an anonymous user is an existing user of SetAlarmClock.net on line services without removing the anonymity of that user.

While Google Analytics cookies are targeting cookies which use a unique ID and can track your visits around different websites, the information collected is anonymous and you will not be personally identifiable to either Google or SetAlarmClock.net

_Demographics and interests reporting_ – Understand how SetAlarmClock.net’s site audience breaks down by age, gender, and interests.

Google analytics data sharing settings enabled: – Google products & services – SetAlarmClock.net shares Google Analytics data with Google to help improve Google’s products and services.

_Benchmarking_ – SetAlarmClock.net contributes anonymous data to an aggregate data set to enable features like benchmarking and publications that can help SetAlarmClock.net understand data trends. All identifiable information about SetAlarmClock.net’s website is removed and combined with other anonymous data before it is shared with others.

_Technical support_ – Google technical support representatives have access to SetAlarmClock.net’s Google Analytics data and account when necessary to provide service and find solutions to technical issues.

_Opt-out:_ Users may opt out of Google Universal Analytics’ use of cookies by visiting the Google Universal Analytics opt-out page.

_Storage Location:_ Google stores the information collected by the cookie on secure Google servers.

### Google Adwords

#### What is Google Adwords?

Google Adwords is an advertising analytics service provided by Google, Inc.

#### How Google Adwords Works

Adwords uses temporary cookies that are stored on a user’s computer for a limited period. Only pages that a user has visited containing the Google conversion code are tracked.

Google does not collect or store personal information. Conversions are not isolated: This means that Google or SetAlarmClock.net cannot match conversion data to specific customers. Instead Google or SetAlarmClock.net can just see overall data for ads and keywords.

_Opt out:_ There is no opt out available for this third party cookie. If you do not wish for this third party cookie to be on your computer, please do not click on Google Ads.

_Storage Location:_ Google stores the information collected by the cookie on secure Google servers.

### Google Adwords Remarketing

#### What is Google Adwords Remarketing?

AdWords Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioural targeting service provided by  
Google Inc.

#### How Google Adwords Remarketing works

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to SetAlarmClock.net’s site. It means that SetAlarmClock.net advertises to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on a SetAlarmClock.net site, for example not completing a product application. This could be in the form of an advertisement on a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to SetAlarmClock.net websites.

Google does not collect or store personal information.

_Opt out:_ Users may opt-out of Adwords Remarketing use of cookies by visiting the [Adwords Remarketing opt-out page.](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)

_Storage Location:_ Google stores the information collected by the cookie on secure Google servers.

### DoubleClick by Google

#### What is DoubleClick?

DoubleClick leverages a 64-bit persistent cookie tied to the doubleclick.net domain. The contents of the cookie consist exclusively of a single string of random characters. DoubleClick cookies expire two years after they are placed on the web browser. Only pages that a user has visited containing the DoubleClick code are tracked. DoubleClick also uses Remarketing pixels – a pixel is a small, invisible piece of code that tells DoubleClick to save visitors’ cookies to SetAlarmClock.net websites on a list. Third-party vendors, including DoubleClick (owned by Google), then use the cookies to serve ads on sites across the internet based on someone’s past visits to SetAlarmClock.net websites.

DoubleClick does not collect or store personal information.

_Opt-out:_ Users may opt-out of Double Click cookies by visiting the Doubleclick opt-out page.

_Storage Location:_ Google stores the information collected by the DoubleClick cookie on secure Google servers.

For more information go to [Privacy Policies ](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)and [Privacy Ads.](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

### How to manage and disable cookies?

For instructions on blocking and deleting cookies, see the privacy and help documentation of your specific browser’s website. If you use more devices and/or browsers you will need to disable cookies on each device and on each browser separately. Here are the locations of the cookie settings for all major web browsers:

  * [Internet Explorer](https://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies) – Tools > Internet Options > Privacy tab.
  * [Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.com/en-US/kb/Cookies#w_cookie-settings) – Tools > Options > Privacy menu.
  * [Safari](https://www.apple.com/safari/features.html#security) – Edit > Preferences > Privacy menu.
  * [Chrome users](https://www.google.com/intl/en/chrome/browser/privacy/) – Settings > Content Settings > Privacy > Cookies.

If you limit the ability of our websites to set cookies, this may prevent you from using certain features of our website properly and your user experience – which will no longer be personalised for you – may deteriorate. You may also be able to opt out from certain cookies through third party cookie management sites. Disabling cookies may prevent you from using certain parts of our website. If you delete your cookies from the browser, you may need to remember to re-install opt-out cookies.

For more information about how to manage cookies, including opting-out of different types of cookies please visit: [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/)

You can also find more information about how to opt-out of targeting cookies by visiting: [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)
